daytradingforexlive.com 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy

Day Trading Forex Live is completely committed to keeping your information private.

Day Trading Forex Live created this privacy policy in an effort to illustrate their strong concern for keeping your information safe and private! The following information details how Day Trading Forex Live gathers and stores your personal information when viewing www.daytradingforexlive.com

Day Trading Forex Live only collects information from those who willing decide to provide contact information. For example, those viewing www.daytradingforexlive.com may decide to join the free mailing list. Members who join the Day Trading Forex Live Bank Trading Course provide their name, email, and phone number by choice.

The personal information collected is never sold, rented, traded, or given away free. All personal information is kept private and at no time will any third party intentionally be given access to this information.

By providing contact information to Day Trading Forex Live you are acknowledging and allowing Day Trading Forex Live to contact you for the purpose of providing free education, promotional material, site changes, or any other reason related to the business of trading and/or Day Trading Forex Live.

By viewing www.daytradingforexlive.com you agree to allow statistical analyses of your visit. You also agree to the use of cookies for the purpose of tracking views, speeding up user experience, or tracking for any other reason deemed necessary.

At any time users have the right to “opt out” of further contact. Every email sent will have an “unsubscribe” button located at the bottom. Users may also opt out by sending an email to daytradingforexlive@gmail.com

Access to the Day Trading Forex Live member database is restricted to staff members responsible for site maintenance of all kinds and customer support. Member information is never sold, rented, traded, of given away free.

Neither the Site(s) nor the Service are directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at daytradingforexlive@gmail.com. We never intentionally collect information from anyone under the age of 18.

Day Trading Forex Live retains the right to change any part of the privacy policy at any time without prior notice. When a change has been made all users will be notified of changes immediately. By viewing www.daytradingforexlive.com you agree to all information contained in the privacy policy.

Contact Day Trading Forex Live  
Please contact Day Trading Forex Live in regards to any questions about the privacy policy.

Day Trading Forex Live  
11656 S. Shaver Rd. Apt 2  
Schoolcraft, MI 49087  
Phone 1 (269) 929-6414  
Support@DayTradingForexLive.com
